{
    "subject": "resource/Dharma_Chakram",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#label",
    "object": "Dharma Chakram",
    "human_readable": "The label of Dharma Chakram is Dharma Chakram.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9664933085441589,
            "question": "What is the label of Dharma Chakram?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8110587000846863,
            "question": "What significance does the label 'Dharma Chakram' hold?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7399664521217346,
            "question": "Is Dharma Chakram a concept or an object?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7084169983863831,
            "question": "In what context is Dharma Chakram used?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6675723195075989,
            "question": "How is Dharma Chakram defined?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6241915822029114,
            "question": "Can you provide more information about Dharma Chakram?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5757794976234436,
            "question": "Is there a story or legend associated with Dharma Chakram?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5640767216682434,
            "question": "What makes Dharma Chakram unique?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5570027828216553,
            "question": "Are there any other terms related to Dharma Chakram?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5202625393867493,
            "question": "What are some examples of Dharma Chakram in practice?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The label of Dharma Chakram is Dharma Chakram.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4150_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other terms related to Dharma Chakram?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4150_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What makes Dharma Chakram unique?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4150_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a story or legend associated with Dharma Chakram?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4150_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4150_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4150_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4150_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4150_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4150_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4150_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4150_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4150_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4150_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4150_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer to your query:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThis is because the documents contain information about the Dharma Chakra, including its representation in Buddhist teachings, its significance in Hinduism, and its appearance as a symbol on various flags. The documents also mention books with the title \"The Dharma Chakra\" which suggests that the label for this concept is indeed \"Dharma Chakram\" or simply \"Dharma Chakra\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThis response is based on the information provided, where there are multiple references to the Dharmachakra (or Dharma Chakra) in different contexts, confirming that it indeed refers to the \"Wheel of Law\" or a representation of Buddha\u2019s teachings."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}